[Music]
Mike Nelson and his robot pals are caught in an endless chase.
Pursued by a woman whose name is Pearl.
An evil gal who wants to rule the world.
She threw a few things in her purse.
And in her rocket ship she hunts him all across the universe.
I'll get you!
I'll send him cheesy movies.
The worst I can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all.
And I'll monitor his mind.
Now keep in mind Mike can't control where the movies begin or end.
He'll try to keep his sanity with the help of his robot friends.
Robot rules called "Hem-on"
You're on!
Cheat series!
Don't serve a heck me out!
I am ready!
If you're wondering how he eats and breathes.
And other science facts.
Just repeat to yourself it's just a show.
I should really just relax.
Called Mystery Science Theater 3000.
And...
Hi everyone, Mike Nelson here on the satellite of love.
You know recently Tom Servo acquired this coat from a catalog.
And it was comfort rated to 20 below or something.
Anyway now Tom Servo is really excited about comfort rating.
10 below Mike!
And he's comfort rating everything on the ship.
15 above Mike!
Frankly I think it's just another case of Tom Servo carrying something to a ridiculous extreme.
Oh is that what you think Mike?
Well look you're wearing bologna.
And now you're suggesting bologna has no insulating properties?
Well I don't know but I can't...
It's really cold, you're nude and all you have is some bologna.
And you refuse to wear it because it's absurd.
That's really sad Mike.
Okay fine go ahead. Comfort rate the bologna.
I think I will.
Christmas in the Hamptons.
A family ski weekend at Wreckenridge.
A fire.
Wind.
This cozy bologna is comfort rated to 25 below.
Hey Servo, you told me this crowbar was comfort rated to 15 below.
And it's just a little chilly in my room.
And it's not doing the trick even for that.
Well I really I...
Oh okay I admit it.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
I'm pulling these comfort ratings out of thin air.
Thin air I tell you!
That's okay. It's alright.
Hey Mike you're pretty comfortable.
Mind if I uh...
Fine go ahead. Comfort rating.
This 100% breathable waterproof Mike, surround me a little more will you Mike?
Will help you stay toasty.
Comfort rated to 10 below.
Available in tope, mauve, trestle, wall, staunch, cheese, tape, fold.
Tape? We'll be right back.
Flank. Stu.
And it's also available in blink, pant, tense, think, pawl.
How about twerp? Can I get it in twerp?
Twerp's on backorder right now. Should be about 4 to 36 weeks.
Great!
Any of those brain guys are calling.
Greetings you whose bodies are the leaves of your lesser beings.
Waiter! Waiter!
Where were we?
Uh yes refresh at once. It has come to our attention that you have reached the apex of...
Hi are you my waiter? Good because there's not enough parmesan on my clams casino.
And my nutritionist specifically said that I should have plenty...
That's it. We've had it. You are no longer needed in your corporeal form.
You ought to be dissected and displayed in our museum.
The hell?
At first you will obey our command.
What? Me? Fight Bobo to the death?
I will do no such... do... strong... can't...
You shall use the traditional weapons of our land. You the deadly double-bladed karangu.
And you ape the sea snail.
Sea snail?
Must... kill... ape... companion... no!
And now losers in the sky you too shall obey our psychic command.
Huh? I'm not getting any... are you?
No. Not a thing.
Oh no. Let me help you observer.
I see snail!
I tell you what. Why don't I just come up here... there.
That'll do the trick I think.
Whoa!
Doc!
What? No. No I can't. I don't...
Wait. Wait. I'm getting something. I... I... sound... it sounds like...
I...t... I...t... right him?
Ignite him.
Night... night him?
Delight him.
Light him.
Contrite.
Requite.
Sight.
Vegemite.
It's a vegemite.
I'm getting... uh... uh... vegemite.
There's a tall... full of...
What are you doing?
Touch him. Touch him.
Very windy like...
Fight?
Fight!
It's fine! This one is right here.
I don't think the dog is wrong.
We're gonna miss leading you know.
Get him!
Come here you!
Take this!
Oh!
You piece of face!
You piece of face let out dude!
Yeah! Okay. Alright. Who's next?
Yeah. Pearl Forrester has got it going on.
Alright. Now, Siriffic, your movie today is Terror from the Year 5000.
Uh oh. You got a little something?
Ha ha!
Preacher fun!
Yeah!
Come here you little seven!
I know you got it!
Oh! We got movie time!
Got him.
Tell the world go away!
Present movie!
It's a hypodermic plane.
Are you sure this is what you want to present movie?
Surrender Dorothy!
In the year 1947, man broke through the sound barrier.
They thought they were so cool.
What was I saying? I got distracted by the rocket.
In the year 1958, man launched the first satellite and pierced the space barrier.
And yet I can't get my pants back by Thursday.
Now in an isolated area of Central Florida, man struggles to penetrate the most imposing barrier of all.
Dames!
The time barrier!
Here, Professor Howard Erling, nuclear physicist, probes relentlessly into the future.
Only to unleash upon the world, Terror!
From the year 5000!
Are you ready for Terror?
I've been waiting my whole life to do a Joyce Holden movie.
Dental technicians from the year 5000!
Well, I've been probing relentlessly for hours. I'm grabbing me a juice box.
Only Terror should be underway any moment now, so if you'll just be patient.
How do you want your burrito, sir?
I realize now I may have oversold the Terror at the beginning, and for that I apologize.
Earnest repairman from the year 5000!
You look like Kraftwerk.
You look like the guy who's on keyboards back there.
[whistling]
There seems to be some sort of delay on the Terror. I'll just go on back and check what the problem is.
How is it?
It's terrifying!
We should be there in a minute.
We have a flavor leak! We're losing flavor, gentlemen!
Oh, they got the sparkler channel.
Paul Manship's knock-kneed nude.
The Shroud of Suzanne Somers.
Professor, look quickly! A woman!
A woman in here? Hide the comic books!
Oh, another statue. For a moment I thought you were...
A moment it looked life-size.
Just an optical illusion. No doubt a refracted image.
[alarm]
The pop-tarts are done.
Quick, help me shut it off! We pushed the voltage too high!
All this to run the Jacuzzi match.
Hans Comrade and Mike Nichols in Altered States.
And right in the middle of my party tape. Damn.
That settles it.
We don't know crap.
No more forced experiments until we get outside verification.
It just hurts too much.
We've been going over the same ground for months now.
And we'll continue to do so until we're thoroughly sure of why this happens.
No, we don't want to.
Not for my money we won't.
Victor, when you invested your money in this project, I knew it was more for personal than scientific reasons.
Backstory?
But I accepted your help only on condition that I make the decisions.
But Dad...
Look, Professor, I never pretended to be a scientist.
Or an actor.
But I know one thing. My old man didn't get rich waiting for outside verification.
Exposition?
He just plowed ahead and he got results.
I'm sorry, Victor.
I have to spank you.
But the kind of results you're after involve too much risk.
If you want to withdraw your help, you know I wouldn't walk out.
And you know why.
I need to be pinker and moister.
Alright then. We've got work to do.
Let's get busy and try to neutralize that statue.
Let's neutralize the hell out of it.
My first statue neutralization.
Hi, big boy.
Northwest Orient.
And the statue embarks on its triumphant world tour.
Hey, there's Hitchcock.
And so you see, Mother, I've been significantly influenced by cubists.
Pummy!
And former sweat hog.
Pile!
Miss Blake, would you come in, please?
Could you read this telegram?
Yes, but I can't make hands or tails of it.
Well, there's no need to lash out.
Listen to this.
Do not understand why you have not replied to my letters.
You have proof that I am not insane.
Love, Mom.
Please establish date of origin of statue to your own satisfaction.
Wire reply immediately.
Professor Howard Earling, Spooner Beach, Florida.
What statue?
What Florida?
Have we received anything from Professor Earling?
There was a package in the morning's mail.
I was just going to open it. Perhaps that's it.
Why must you spew your rage?
What do you hear?
Truth that I am not insane.
That's what I need.
He's a museum curator, yet he has starving artist paintings on the wall.
Yeah.
Would you stop screaming at me, Miss Blake?
God!
Well, now let's see what we've got here.
Frau Gille.
Oh, hee hee, hee hee, oh my.
Well, he's a drill sergeant curator.
Drop and give me 20, statue.
How old would you say this is?
It doesn't look old to me.
It's a matter of fact, it looks new.
Brant new.
She needs to deal with her rage.
Really?
Now, why do you suppose Professor Earling would send me a statue that's obviously modern
and ask me to establish its date of origin?
Isn't that what you do with that vacuum cleaner, carbon 14 thing you're always talking about?
Find out how old things are?
Miss Blake, you should know that that carbon 14 thing, as you call it,
is only the most advanced method known to mankind for establishing the precise date of origin of archaeological artifacts.
Well, that's what I said. Find out how old things are.
Women equals dumb.
Oh, right, Miss Blake, you have it your way.
I'll have to chase you around the desk now.
What are you going to do with it?
Miss Blake, ever since I studied with Professor Earling, I've been a little afraid of him.
He's a 50-foot cyclops.
He says, "Establish date of origin of statue."
Just like in WW2.
Well, that's exactly what I'm going to do.
Oh, sir, should you?
Well, I could establish the date and stuff.
So now we're in London, Tokyo, whatever.
What, did he lose his bottom half during the war?
I've just been playing Barbies with the statues all night.
It can't be minus. It can't be.
I must have been mistaken by calculations.
Six plus one is ten.
It's minus. It means this statue wasn't made until the year 5200 A.D.
I'm calling General Picasso.
I'll have to storm the beaches at MoMA.
He's trying to figure out the angle of his flat top.
Listen, you sheet-el.
Put me down.
I don't know why Earling sent you to me, but this much I do know.
You can't exist.
Say?
Not here and not now.
Not for another 3,000 years.
I'm just sore, that's all. Sorry.
I can't wait to see the Mapplethorpe exhibit.
Dr. Robert had just died today from haircut injuries sustained from a severe flat top.
Oh, I'm sorry, Dr. Hinton.
But I slashed your tires.
Do you have cartoon music playing in your head, too?
Goodness. Did you spend a night here?
Nothing happened, and if it did, it was consensual.
Looks like it.
Did you find out how old the statue is?
Oh, sure.
According to the eminent Dr. Hedges, renowned expert in the field of dating archaeological objects,
that statue was made in the year 5200 A.D.
If man is still a flea.
Is it still horribly old?
Old?
Do you hear me clearly, Miss Blake?
I said 5200 A.D., not B.C.
By my calculations, that statue doesn't even exist, and it won't exist for another 3,000 years.
Have you been free-basing again, sir?
I know. I sound like I'm a raving drunk, even to myself.
Oh, I didn't mean that.
Call the Eastside Testing Laboratories and tell them we're going to send the statue over to them,
and we want a metallurgical and chemical analysis right away.
Yes, sir.
I can't hear you, maggot!
Now there's an interesting sample.
Now there's an interesting line read.
Wait. Don't know yet.
Remember, when making a dramatic film, be sure to use genuine actors.
Well, don't let me intrude.
I touch the woman.
Bye, gorgeous.
I detect jolly time.
Hey, that thing's radioactive.
It's hot as a firecracker.
I'm not sure if it's a firecracker.
That thing's radioactive. It's hot as a firecracker.
Get that bucket of water, quick.
No, that's a bucket of chicken.
I can't swim!
Put some lead shielding on that thing and hurry.
I'll just run down to Lead Shielding Hut and take care of that.
I hope you like rock ports.
How dangerous is it?
Well, it's hard to say exactly.
My guess is that if you were constantly exposed to it for a week, you'd be a sick man.
In two weeks, you'd be dead.
I was wondering about that extra arm on my back.
This Professor Earling, would he have any reason to want to do harm to you?
Once I wiped a booger on his dashboard.
Testing.
Well, maybe I've been seeing too much TV.
But Uncle Miltie's hot.
Has it ever occurred to you that if you suddenly drop dead, you'd be the victim of an almost perfect crime?
That's ridiculous. Professor Earling is an old friend of mine.
Well, like they say, with a friend like that, you don't need an enemy.
Drive not ready. Abort, retry, fail.
Did you have any luck on that long-distance call to Professor Earling?
The Splinter Beach Opera House, do they have no phone listed in that name?
Uncoverable disk error. Data may be lost.
I see.
I'd better have my hair sharpened while I'm out.
Will you call the airlines and arrange for a flight for me down to Splinter Beach, Florida?
Uh-huh. Go shopping.
And then wire to Professor Earling and tell him the time of my arrival.
Get Lancome.
And just to be on the safe side, I think you should arrange for a rental car at the airport.
And have lunch with girls.
Okay.
Don't be like three-pound salted nut rolls.
Tell me, my deadly little girlfriend.
Will you marry me?
Are there any more at home like you?
Yes, and here they come. Lots of deadly little girlfriends for everybody.
Ladies and gentlemen, the Beatle.
That's stuck in reverse. Save yourselves.
[muffled singing]
Well, I'm sorry, sir. We only have Bonnie and Clyde's death car left, but we'll just charge it for a compact.
What? What about his luggage? How could they leave us hanging?
Did he make hotel reservations? There are huge holes in this movie.
Yeah.
He's hovercrafting.
Martin Borman, stock car racer.
Suddenly this movie is an excruciatingly detailed travelogue.
Probably went back and got another car.
Okay, let's try this scene again.
Is that car following me?
Well, your grandma likes her, Glenlivet.
Is Professor Early, would he have any reason to want to do harm to you?
Michael, why don't you answer me?
No, he'd be dead.
He'd be the victim of an almost perfect crime.
Oh, and your dog called and said to kill your family.
Can't shake real estate development.
Terror from the year 5000 turned out to be a Ford with bad brakes.
Tell me what to do, boys. Come on.
Can't you just feel the terror from the year 5000?
Wait, you left your hat at the rental counter.
But they speed cautiously through school zones.
Squeezeably soft.
Well, you proved you can drive. Now what do we play?
Grace Kelly and Frank Sutton in to catch a pile.
Dr. Hedges, I presume.
How did you know my name?
You're Mrs. Lady, right?
I'm Claire Early. Professor Early's daughter.
Daughter.
As soon as I got to the airport, they told me I just missed you.
I'm not in the scene.
How is your father? Is he well? I mean, is he all right?
You mean is he crazy, Dr. Hedges? No, Dad's perfectly sane.
But me? I am out there.
Well, the telegram and the statue.
I sent them.
Dad doesn't know a thing about them.
You sent them?
Well, I thought when you didn't answer his letters,
if you saw the statue and examined it with your own eyes,
it might shock you into some sort of a reply.
Brain is timed out. Please try later.
I never received any letters.
And as for the statue shocking me, it certainly did.
Then you were able to establish its age.
That statue is dangerous. It's radioactive.
I shouldn't have packed it in nuclear waste, sir.
Yes, I think I'm entitled to an explanation.
I was trying to make you sterile.
Of course you are.
And I'll give it to you as soon as we get to the house.
So if you'll just follow me.
He should have followed his bliss and became a gym coach.
You think?
All these random scenes simply abut each other to form a movie.
This scene was recreated from eyewitness accounts.
It's not a good movie, but there is plenty of off-street parking.
Where are you taking me? To our place. It's on an island.
See? Water implies island.
An island?
Mm-hmm.
I'll explain on the way over.
It's too curator-centric to know what an island is.
Who's that?
Hamilton Jordan. How the hell do I know?
Oh, that's Angelo.
He's the chief cook and bottle washer.
Two, three...
Excuse me, miss, but how do I know that you're Professor Erling's daughter?
'Cause I've got his figure.
Victor was right.
Scientists are the biggest old fogies in the world.
Who's Victor?
Victor Buono, my boyfriend.
He's a man.
Four, five, six, seven...
Here's my driver's license and my card registration.
Her card registration?
Is that enough or would you like my birth certificate?
No, that's satisfactory. Thank you.
You sure?
Excuse me, I don't mean to seem so suspicious, but I'm not.
Excuse me, I don't mean to seem so suspicious, but all this is kind of new to me.
I've never been away from home.
I thought scientists were great explorers of the unknown.
I'll do my exploring in the laboratory, if you don't mind.
I get my kicks above the way sunshine.
Now what's going on?
Who's that other guy?
Where are we going?
What is this fluid under my feet?
What happened to the day ball?
Let's chip in and buy this movie a life.
Yeah.
I think this is our boat. I can't really tell.
Regis, what are you doing here?
And then the local newspaper said that Dad's theory about crossing the time barrier was ridiculous.
This is safe, right?
He was disqualified for top secret work, so the missile center fired him.
Fired him? Why?
Folks, I can't see the lake.
They said he was unreliable.
A potential security risk.
Could you get off the prow of the boat?
That was ridiculous.
We both laughed at first, then we began to get anonymous phone calls.
Well, from who?
They said Dad was a traitor and that he ought to leave town.
Is that why you moved to this island?
Well, partly. Mainly.
Well, no.
Because Dad's electrical equipment is so powerful that it messes up TV reception for miles around.
I see.
Also, Dad and I are married and the town doesn't like that.
It appears to be daytime suddenly.
It's nice.
Ah, guess I was mistaken. Oops.
Sorry, I've got a really old Johnson here.
And the motor doesn't work either.
Thank you.
Ah, it's an instant classic, Mike.
Good work.
Thank you.
Tara awaits patiently.
Glad Hume Cronin's one versatile actor.
Miss Claire, you think maybe your father's working that contraption of his again?
Take your pardon?
Even if he is, it's never bothered us this far out.
I'll bet that's what caused it.
When you said his experimental equipment was powerful, it was the understatement of the century.
Next day, I guess.
You want to eat, you have to work.
This is the kind of texture that other movies would leave out.
Yeah, those other movies are often referred to as good movies.
I bet you as a good movie.
Hey, look!
Jake, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Hey, evolved beyond body, brain, guys, thank you.
What are they?
Having evolved beyond bodies and beyond language, guess what else we've evolved beyond?
The give up.
Oh, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know.
Food.
You know, this is a small pill to be so nutritionally all-encompassing.
I would imagine in this tiny pill is the equivalent of a full day's supply of nutrients.
I'll bet you right, Ray Maflavin Breath.
One pill, perhaps.
Though were you to eat only one, you would hardly derive full benefit from our remarkable pills.
Oh, okay, so two or three pills, fine, that's got to be all you need given how advanced you guys are and all.
Shh, with the simple use of what we call a spoon.
Do you understand?
Simply place a generous portion in your mouth and repeat the process.
So, a bowl then, a smallish bowl and you're set for the day, right?
No, it would be pretty light if you held it to a bowl, right?
Four or five bowls.
Eight, ten bowls of our non-food pills every day.
That should be enough to keep your weight up.
The weight of your body, which of course you've evolved beyond.
Well, what is the point of having these pills if you have to eat so many of them?
I mean, what is the point?
Well, it's very hard game.
Well, even fifteen bowls a day.
Well, I mean, I just, I look at our non-food and I balloon right up.
This guy, he can eat all he wants and look at him, he stays so thin.
Look at him, look at this guy.
Oh, that's great.
Well, what I've done here though is I've made some parmesan encrusted pill cakes
and I just put some of these through a ricer here and you just form them into a patty.
Can I get a shot of that please?
And you can see that they're just very lightly done and that's a light meal you can have any time.
It's just some chanterelles and some wood ears and a little bit of shallots.
I'll tame them in a pan for about five minutes
and we're going to be back to enjoy these things right after this.
So, we'll see you later and I bid you peace.
The door leads into the abyss.
These smockers is begging to be let out.
Sorry mister, can we have our ball?
Oh great, a sparrow from the year 5000 crashed into the window.
The lab is in a tenement building?
Finish the experiment, collect the rent from 4B.
God, it never ends.
There's Uncle Joe, he's moving kind of slow at the junction.
Oh, now the old guy's moving fast.
What time is it Victor?
I sat down to do a little reading before dinner, fell fast asleep.
I don't know, I just woke up from a nap myself.
It's four.
Dad, look who's with me, Dr. Hedges from New York.
He says hi.
Ah, Bob Hedges, this is a wonderful surprise.
Can't speak in row, sorry.
Victor, do you realize what this means?
At last we'll have outside verification of our experiments.
I don't want outside verification.
I wish you'd told me you'd sent for Dr. Hedges.
I'd like to have been prepared for him.
You know, do my hair and my nails iron my skirt.
Doctor, were you playing kid ball in the lab again?
Oh, it's the front windshield of any 1977 Buick.
Ew, I never want to see him trot again.
No, don't trot.
Oh my God, could it be?
No, he had an extra pane of glass.
Oh God.
He has a pear-shaped body and upsettingly hairless arms.
So you knew the statue was radioactive?
Yes, Bob.
What I want to know is why didn't somebody tell me?
You've been told never to touch anything in the laboratory.
You girl.
That should have been enough.
Posture.
You needn't be so mean, Victor.
You know, you're not my husband yet.
Unfortunately, the appearance of so much radioactivity
has forced us to stop our experiments
until we find out much more about the powers we're dealing with, Bob.
Not a good pose.
But weren't you working in your laboratory when we arrived?
No.
Victor and I haven't operated the apparatus for days now.
A TED vessel, international coffee mall.
Dr. Hedges, you must be exhausted after your trip.
You're right, Victor.
Come on, Bob.
I'll have Angela get you set upstairs.
Good night, Dean.
Well, actually, I'm feeling kind of perky.
Well, good night.
Huge radio back there.
Now, my fish belly white fiancé.
Alone at last.
Except that you're still here.
The room was decorated in early great pots.
Of all the silly things to do.
Trying to melt a cow.
Getting that pompous Hedges down here.
Jimmy Carter.
I thought that's what you and Dad wanted someone to verify.
You wanted someone to verify your findings.
Yeah, verify?
Mm-hmm.
Can't you tell he's laughing up his sleeve at us?
It's your hair shelf he's laughing at.
No?
Mm-hmm.
Did you see the way he smiled when your father told him that statue actually did come from the...
There's a malaise over there.
There is not.
He looked like a boy psychiatrist listening to his pet loon.
Victor.
You're pasty and hairless.
He just didn't understand that Dad was serious, that's all.
Besides, I think he's cute.
For a drill instructor.
Cute?
In a Sergeant Carter-ish way, yeah.
Victor, you're not just a wee bit jealous, are you?
Who, me jealous of that overgrown boy scare?
Oh, well, I thought if you were, there's something I ought to tell you.
I'm Jay Davidson.
Oh?
He's a moist, pillowy, Dwayne Hickman.
Don't hate me.
I believe I'm experiencing stagflation.
He used freezehold on his eyebrows.
Oh, he just holds his fish lips there and she does all the work.
God, what a brave actress.
Angelo.
Yes, sir?
What are you doing?
Professor Owen says Dr. Hedges is going to sleep in here.
What?
But the door is locked.
I don't remember having no key to this room.
Well, leave that door alone.
There it is.
Put his things in Myra.
I'll make him play Chutes and Ladders all night.
God, I can't, I can't move, I can't move.
I...
Oh, moved.
Wait, I'm on the same floor again.
Architecture by M.C. Escher.
He's trying to reanimate a dead slinky.
Oh, looks like the UPS guy.
But he has no package.
Mike, he's a right mind.
Professor Erling, the door to the spare room is locked and Angelo seems to have lost the key.
I had him put Bob's things in Myra.
Well, I hate to point you out, but it's no trouble.
It's only for one night, Bob.
I'll have Angelo get it open tomorrow for you.
The riveting and action-packed accommodation scene.
Wow.
His human body is 70% mucus.
Ernest Borgnine sleeps peacefully.
The terrible aching crush I had on my roommate from the year 5000.
Psst.
You want to play with my hot wheels?
I got the looped up.
You want to play with my hot wheels? I got the looped to loop track.
There's an 8x10 of Victor Kayam on his bureau.
I'm going to put on his pants.
They're still warm.
Don't want to be on the single guy anymore.
He likes to secretly dress in men's clothes.
Oops, ran into his fuller brush samples.
He's got his own little junior scientist bed.
Why don't I just lay on him? I know I want to.
Okay, so he feels compelled to hide from a stranger the fact that he's getting a drink of water.
Apparently.
I think he's embarrassed by his midnight humectifying sessions.
Sure.
He looks like a walking butter sculpture, don't you think?
Why don't he?
Listen, you can hear his hair grow.
Oh, I was having the nicest dream.
I was eating a butt steak with Vince Lombardi and Bear Bryant.
You know, grown men just should not wear official pajama outfits.
Just what do you think you're doing in your own house, young man?
I'll just put on his pants then.
He was in Miss Havisham's apartment.
Just got to see my vacation slides from Knott's Berry Farm again.
Yep, doesn't get any better than this. Pajama tops, dungarees and a box of men.
Well, I'll have to creep out in the hall without my cufflinks. I guess it's embarrassing.
This is the same sumptuously detailed set that was later used in the Age of Innocence.
Or was it Sense and Sensibility?
I think it was Barfly.
Yeah!
That's it.
I suppose you're wondering when the terror from the year 5000 will show up.
Well, my apologies, it is taking rather long, but we're trying to pace ourselves.
I'm going to the city to be a stud.
Please, that's a hideous thought.
Sorry.
He was a small oily man.
Pants, pants, pants, pants.
Herbalife products in one hand, Amway in the other.
Oh, hi Dave.
I'm not Dave, I'm a simple fern.
I'm going where the pit stains suit my clothes.
Incoming!
I don't have to act if I don't wanna.
No.
The free little Samsonite.
He's part of the luggage liberation front.
I think he's trying to skip suitcases.
His relationship with his ventriloquist dummy went bad.
In the remake, this went to Artie Johnson.
I was looking for you on the bay side of the island.
That's where we usually go swimming.
What's wrong with this?
It's a swamp.
Nothing.
Except there's no place to change.
Well, I've got mine on.
No, no!
He's made entirely of baby's bottoms.
Why don't you go behind the trees and change?
He has tiny nipples.
Can I trust you?
Call it calculated risk.
We've got Noel Coward to punch up this dialogue.
Ow, ow, ow.
Everyone from this era looks like they worked for NASA.
Hey, Claire, why do they call this Leech Pond?
Always dive head first into an unfamiliar lake.
It's like watching Margaret Truman be flirtatious.
Hey, this is great!
Come on, get changed!
There, I've decided.
Yeah, it's really great in here, Claire.
Just have to watch out for the chiggers.
And the soccer fish.
And the alligator guards.
And the car engines.
But it's great!
Sorry, teenage boys of the '50s.
This'll have to do.
A curator ran aground today,
spilling millions of gallons of vitalis.
Forgive me.
I'll drown myself and rip your thoughts.
Cool, like humidor.
What, is she showering now?
Oh, yeah, wow!
She's all there, boys.
100% scrawny spinster.
Suddenly, she's turned into Mrs. Pinchot.
Swimming bonnet from Amish Beachwear Fashions of Charm, Ohio.
They whacked toonces.
Well, they killed a made canary, so they had to do them.
Neck Injury Theater presents...
You wanted to eat fishes, not sleep with them.
Yum, yum, yum, yum.
Ah, what the hell that'll do.
Man was clearly born in a barn.
It is great.
I stepped on a bowhead and got bit by a water moccasin,
but it's great!
Hey, I just stepped on a rusty can.
These deer flies are eating me alive, isn't it great?
Now I'll give him tetanus with this rusty nail here.
Hey!
What's the matter?
Something bit me.
Maybe it was an alligator.
Come on, let's get out of here.
With a mouth like this...
Dine.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm not kidding.
My brother was killed by a stick.
Dangerous horseplay can be fun.
Yeah.
No, please.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
Ha ha, I won.
He's dead.
He's dressed for a baton.
I'm not certain, but I just may have it going on.
I gotta kill a rabbit for you.
Curator of the Black Lagoon.
All right for me to come out now?
Just two more hours.
You found the alligators?
Ha ha, I don't get it.
Dr. Hedges, Professor Erland says he and Mr. Victor
are running a laboratory now.
And they're nude.
Oh, good.
Hurry up and get dressed, Bob.
I'll be right out.
Just drinking some jiggers.
Now you're gonna see something fantastic.
Thanks to Pert Plus.
All right, Victor.
That's the cue ball.
So the juices stay locked inside, huh?
It's wonderful.
Haley's M.O. from the year 5,000.
Congratulations, Doctor.
You've managed to turn milk into bowling trophies.
And once I turned a hat into a shoe.
I'm afraid the souffle has fallen, gentlemen.
Oh, the pressed coffee I've always dreamed of.
Boy, this is remarkable.
No, it isn't. Shut up.
The bottle you put in there is completely transformed.
Not transformed, exchanged, traded.
Yeah.
What do you mean, traded?
Think, though.
Throughout human history,
what has been the first activity of explorers of any new region?
Genocide? Slavery?
Disease blankets spreading?
That make me, I suppose.
Nobel, barter, trade.
Coupons, what?
Coupons, credit lines, no payments to the year 5,000.
To Marco Polo with the Chinese.
To Columbus with the Indians.
Or in our own time, Bird and Perry with the Eskimos.
Or Kluban of the planet Frau Hall.
Trade.
Do you mean you actually think that you've contacted human beings of the future?
Well, there's no other possible explanation.
Uh-huh.
No disrespect, Professor, but
everything you've been showing me has all the earmarks of a magician's trick.
Oh, come on.
Professor, we're wasting our time.
He's drying my oils.
Professor, do you mind if I sort of reshuffle the cards?
What do you mean, Bob?
Well, supposing I take an object now on the spur of the moment,
something that hasn't been prepared.
Uh-huh.
And we try to exchange it, as you say.
Are you accusing us of fraud?
No, there's a lot going on here I don't understand.
Mike, why can't you eat three pretzel rods in a minute?
It's all right, Victor, being overly cautious
is an occupation of disease that most archaeologists do.
I'm sorry.
Exactly.
I wonder what our friends of the future would give for this five-betta-kappa key.
Where'd you kype that from?
So he drives a five-betta-kappa?
What?
Mm, ten.
British nights.
Yeah.
Jarrah better not rip me off, man.
They sent back a cineburst.
Well, whatever it is, it's not as spectacular as the last time.
Yeah, not to yours.
Treasures from the future in about an hour.
Hello, magic future person talking thing which says comes hello, exchange from futuristic...
Hello?
No, no, only Daddy Touch.
It's a neko wafer from the year 5,000.
Shiny, pretty, huh.
Who?
Ellie May.
Hmm.
Why is it impossible?
What is it?
There are Greek letters on the other side.
Hmm.
Two words.
Can you read it?
What does it say?
Lick me.
Says...
Good for bumper ride at Chuck E. Cheese.
Save us.
Save us, collect us, and exchange us for swell prizes.
Stay off the moors!
Godly Roger and Mary Tyler moors.
Ha, ha, ha.
Do, do, do, do.
I'm ashamed.
Hey, Victor, just making time with your girlfriend.
Bob was telling me about this afternoon.
Oh?
Hmm.
Did he also tell you why we won't be getting any further messages?
Because I spill ung ones all over the time machine.
And I will tell you...
The network is down.
Just because that metal disk was a little radioactive, he agreed with your father that we shouldn't dare go any further.
Just for now until we know more.
How are we gonna find out if we don't take a chance once in a while?
It's one thing to be cautious, Hedges.
It's another thing to be just plain scared.
So where were we? Second base?
Victor, you're being rude.
Huh?
You're taking his side, are you?
Well, I am sitting on his hand.
Oh, my.
Look, please don't argue on my account.
Just break up with him and groove on me.
If you give me a hank, I'll go to bed. Have a busy day.
Night, Bob.
Good night, Bob.
See you in a few, honey.
So you wanna talk about our wedding plans?
What are you trying to do?
Sounds like you're just aching for a fight with Bob.
Yeah, so I had the nanites whip me up this time machine based on the one in the movie.
And I was thinking...
And you want to test it out on me 'cause you're afraid of the horrible radiation scarring on that big fleshy body of yours.
Not a problem, Mike.
Oh, gee, thanks, girl. I'd do it, but...
Oh, just bring me a yoo-hoo when it's all over.
Okay, thanks a lot. Really appreciate it.
Now, where do you want me to go, Mike?
Well, I figured I'd set it for Wisconsin.
Shortly after I got the job at the temp agency, just find my family, tell them what happened, tell them I'm okay.
Sure. It'll be kind of fun to meet a real corn-fed farm family.
Crow, I'm not from... Never mind. Here you go.
Goodbye, Aunt Edna, you kook.
Oh, Mike, you're family, they are good people.
Yeah, so did you see them? Did you tell them what happened? Did you tell them I'm okay?
Oh, shoot. Darn, I knew there was something I was supposed to do.
Darn it. See, there was this 4th of July party my third summer there where I almost told them...
Wait, wait, a third summer?
Yeah, before college I was kind of...
Well, how long were you there?
Eleven years. You see, Mike, in time travel you can live a whole lifetime in a single second.
And boy, did I live! Oh, baby.
Well, did they ask about me? Did they miss me at all?
Yeah, I'm sure they did. Hey, your dad, a kook man, I'm telling you.
Grab those pictures out of the time machine, would you?
My dad's pretty reserved, I find.
Elmer Keg Drainer Nelson, reserved? I don't think so.
What else did you grow up in? Hey, and speaking of, I busted your stereo. Sorry about that. I know you wouldn't mind.
Oh, okay.
Oh, that's a good one. Put that on stills.
Oh, all right.
See, me and your dad, we stayed up like three days.
What is this?
Oh, put that next one up.
Dad doesn't party.
We're doing the bunny hop at that little place on the French side of St. Martin.
Oh, and there's the one with Smitty and Murph. Smitty and Murph.
Oh, which reminds me, Smitty and Murph, we rolled your charger.
Total did. I knew you wouldn't mind.
Hey, hey, Curl, I almost hate to ask, is that my old girlfriend Ginger?
You mean Ginger's snap... no.
No, no.
Oh, and there's one with Ginger and me at Stuart Anderson's Cattle Company.
Ginger and me targeting at the Potawatomi...
No, we got boobies on. No, no, no, no.
Ginger.
Augusta National, proud to be restricted.
And action.
Why didn't you mention any of this to me before?
I wasn't sure, but Victor Soram cinches it.
Somehow he's managed to bring life through that apparatus.
That thing I saw him throw in the pond was one of his failures.
But last night he must have gone further.
Frankly, Bob, I'm a little disappointed in you,
these wild accusations against Victor.
Now, now, now.
I'm disappointed after what I saw between you and Claire last night.
Dirty kissing.
Well, let's just say, I think you've lost your objectivity.
Claire has nothing to do with this.
I'm talking about things I've seen with my own eyes.
Now I don't...
Bob, do you remember how you insisted about testing your experiments in your own way?
How you wouldn't even believe your own eyes?
Of course.
Oh, Bob.
Show me.
No, no, no. You don't have to show him bad.
I guess not enough people have seen his waxy abdomen.
Are you going swimming?
Yeah, I am.
Is everyone peeping in this movie?
This is the island of secrets and lies.
Could he at least wear a tube top?
He's got Margaret Thatcher's body shape.
P.F. flyers with new action wedge.
Jiggers are so happy he's back.
En belay.
You took my lady.
He's probably regularly beaten up by a 13-stripe ground squirrel.
And he's built like a 19th century strongman.
It's like a slightly more manly Dan Quayle.
Swimming to depths of two feet.
He himself is illegal dumping.
Action wimp.
His urkel looked like Van Damme.
This is my chemistry set.
He's unleashing the rage of a thousand wedgies.
New moisture pre-soiled action wimp.
He's just down the stream from the rendering plant.
Oh, so let me...
Bar she-balls!
Ah, this is where he accidentally drowns Shelley Winters.
Oh, yeah.
He's a rabbit attacking me.
That boat is perfect for his chihuahua.
Thank you.
Sir Eder's got a lamp ray stuck to his gut already.
The lumberjack competition turns ugly.
I have tubes in my pads.
My magazines expect me to perform all the time.
The epic battle between moist and moisture.
Babe Winkelman and Roland Martin in a fight to the death.
See, his peeping skills are paying off now.
It's oily shirts versus oily skins.
The new swank arrives today.
Fight choreography by Arnold Stang.
He's hitting him with jump cuts.
Angelo knows Wednesday is Prince Spaghetti Day.
Listen, come quick.
Mr. Hedges has beaten up Victor.
And he's getting his skinny ass kicked. It's great.
I'm sorry about the peeping, ma'am.
That's okay, Angelo. Water under the bridge.
There's got to be like snapping turtles in that water. Dead cows.
Unexploded German mines.
Ah, the Peter.
He died as you live. White, moist and bloated.
Yeah.
And out of this fight, a deep abiding friendship is born.
Deep abiding friendship is born.
Look at the oil slick now.
How not to treat your major fun.
Yes.
You've shown me, Hedges. Shown me I was right.
He jumped me. He tried to kill me.
I think I've had enough of your wild accusations.
All right. See for yourself.
That's no Van Heusen.
Those aren't just scratches. They're radiation burns.
That proves he threw a radiator at me.
You know, one picture can say so little.
What the hell?
Rest? Now that we've gone this far?
Victor, we're taking you to the hospital for your own good.
The amount of secondary radiation you've absorbed could be extremely serious.
There's nothing wrong with me.
Oh, wait. Sorry. Yes, there is.
I know what you're trying to do.
You want to get rid of me so you can claim all the glory for yourself.
What time is it?
Victor, for the last time, what caused those scars?
I was caught by a bowl of Pamplona and I picked at it.
Did you materialize some fault, Vile?
I know you are, but what am I?
You're calling me crazy.
One thing I do know, Victor. Your condition is serious.
Age two?
It will take a qualified radiologist to determine just how bad it is.
Now, come on. Get your things together.
We're taking you to the mainland, to the hospital.
Looks like an excommunicated beach boy.
But in the end, they were all married in a lovely private ceremony.
Will the doctor give me a sucker when it's over?
Uncle Meat hangs back.
Poor Angelo is left to peep in an empty house. It's so sad.
Hospital and K through six.
Guess we had to put him to sleep, but I think you'll realize it was for the best.
I can't tell yet. We'll have to run a series of tests first.
When will you know?
We should have the results in two or three hours.
That long?
I'm afraid so. Why don't you run along and get something to eat? Then call us.
All right, Uncle.
Bring tap cleats.
And we'll have the rolled pork roast ready for you, too.
Love you guys.
I'll let you know as soon as possible.
No rush.
Can you spay him while he's here?
Why did they drop me off at the bank? I gotta run over to the hospital to get treated.
I always panic when they say how many. I don't want to go through that again.
No.
Did she reach the doctor?
There's been some confusion. The girl at the desk and sissy went home.
That's impossible. I'd better talk to them.
Now don't get excited. Nothing to do but wait.
It's a good movie in town.
Now we get to watch people watching a movie? What is that all about?
Filmed in glorious black and slightly less black.
The ball tender's a clean old man, isn't he? Clean.
It's quartered and moist. I'm clammy as can be.
Jazz, jazz, jazz, generic jazz.
So we're just watching the characters kill time till the movie starts up again. Great.
Me, too.
Oh, great physical comedy from Bob.
There's Buster Keaton and there's Bob, I say.
This is Chris Kraft of Capcom. The movie is on hold.
T minus 10 minutes to plot resumption.
We have a leak in the narrative and the movie could implode.
Yeah, I'm irradiated. What of it?
Music, generic music, jazz music.
Music.
Hey, you, that usually brings in right.
And discovered America.
June 5th, 1944. I was early.
Angelo, sweet Angelo.
So he went to the hospital, put spats on and came back with his pool cue.
I'm glad they included all this because I was wondering how he's going to get from the boat to the house.
Keys are so bulky and cumbersome. I just...
Let's get eskimo pie.
Damn you, Dave Lennox.
You're the only one who trusts me, time machine.
It's been 10 to 3, about 12 times in this movie.
I'm going to put on machine head and hang out forever. Gary Newman, scientist.
Howdy folks, can I lasso you some round-up menus?
Bob, your Frankenstein was so funny, you should do comedy.
Looks like your whole outfit's having quite a night of it tonight, professor.
That's right, but back to work tomorrow.
Thanks.
Better not count on any work from your assistant tomorrow.
Yeah, just bring the buckaroo burgers, pal.
Why not? Are your drinks that strong?
Now the other fellow, what's his name, Victor?
Was he here?
He was here earlier, got pretty drunk and I finally had to ask him to leave.
Hey Joe, will you turn on the TV set?
Mr. Ruby told me to watch the prison transfer.
Victor, here.
They reluctantly re-enter the plow.
He must be mistaken.
Dad, look at the TV.
The special letterbox edition of static.
What about it?
When Dad read his apparatus here in town, it caused the same kind of disturbance.
Oh, that Ernie Kovacs.
Now that's not all good chumpy just because the TV set goes on the blink.
It is a gold star.
No, Bob, she's right.
It formed a distinctive pattern of interference, that pattern.
What does it mean?
Someone's operating the apparatus, operating it at a higher voltage than ever before.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Okay, who had the fuzzy navel?
Not a crane shot, but an on top of my cousin's truck shot.
Oh, the blemish on his chin is ready to go.
No, no, not the reverb, no.
No, that's just what they'd expect me to do.
Why a MacPherson strut in the foreground?
Ladies and gentlemen, we'll be rejoining our plot momentarily.
We hope the play hasn't caused you to miss connections to any other movies.
Alan Parsons works on his greatest album.
Ah, he's turning himself into Judge Reinhold.
Wait, how did they get from the car to the boat?
They didn't show us.
Come on, Hot Pockets, get done.
Come on.
Still ten to three, the time machine must be leaking.
These are jams, not jellies.
He's on so many illegal mailing lists, it's not funny.
Look at the light.
Send more porn.
They were overworking the trolling mode.
It stopped rooming.
Claire, get out and push.
Maybe if we look at it.
I am Iron Man.
Location scout for this movie must have been a basement dweller.
Uh-huh, you blame me.
I owed you.
One, two, three, four.
Dead clam.
And the Barofsky quartet kicks in.
Now they're leaving the movie again.
He's subletting Clarence Thomas' apartment.
Well, gotta go volunteer at the Youth Center.
At Norton's later years.
Surfside 6.
Back then, product placement was just boats, jackets.
Stop playing with my Magna-Doodle.
My cookies are burning.
The Yule log was booby-trapped.
Get away.
Don't come near me, man.
Please.
Claire, go get some water.
I'll have a water too, thanks Claire.
I'll just make some of my spoon bread and a fresh batch of Johnny cakes.
Mmm.
What's the matter?
Shalom.
Shalom?
I saw a nice glass so I come up the...
Everyone's in the laboratory.
They need your help.
Victor's been hurt.
Yes, ma'am.
You still on for peeping tonight, Angelo?
Don't come near me.
I'm Mickey.
Your face is horrible.
Chocolaty fudgy.
Angelo, take the boat.
Bring Dr. Blair.
Hurry.
For the redemption of Angelo.
It's turning into Petey the dog.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I made oodles of noodles.
Never mind that now.
Get some blankets and hurry.
He's going into shock.
Fine.
Anything else I shouldn't get?
Okay.
He's going to need care for watching.
He could take a turn for the worse at any time.
I'll stay with him.
Fine, but since you don't have a phone here,
it would be best if I send over a nurse.
Phone?
No, fine.
Whatever you think best, doctor.
Face.
It's all burned.
I'm oily, greasy.
Pore is large.
Follicle is clogged.
Please, Victor, please.
Please die.
Don't fight it.
Die.
Oily tinctures.
No pigmentation.
That should at least give us back the power.
Try the switch, Bob.
How do they know he's him?
Like a little bit, what?
Do it again.
It was fun.
Nothing like a little light to dispel a man's fears, is there?
What do you say we dial up a couple of Talskis from the year 5000, hmm?
What do you think it was, Bob?
Scallywags, hooligans, rake hells.
What frightened a man like that?
Was it my comb-over?
I don't know.
What time is it?
I have a feeling that part of the answer is still in those boxes at the bottom of the pond.
Or it's blowing in part of the wind.
You once translated the Iliad, now I walk around in crunchy pants.
Brought to you by the Onan Family Foundation.
Okay.
Terror is going potty now.
She comes from the planet of highway shoulder markers.
What is she, setting a trap line?
Jimmy Carter has disco fever.
How do you like the good wits you're about to itch?
That's a kicky little scarf, huh?
Tying up her boat, looking for worms, lost her contact.
You will jazzercise.
She's being killed by Big Ethel.
I think I stepped on her tail.
Why didn't you tell me you had the skin-dining equipment?
You were the one that was being so secretive.
Of all the plot holes to fill, they chose the scuba gear plot hole.
I promise never not to tell him about scuba gear ever again.
What other common recreational equipment is she keeping from me?
Ah, it's sucking its thumb.
It's one of those fly monkeys, fly monkeys.
You know, he didn't decompress. He's gonna get the bends.
Hi honey, I'm home.
No, no, no, no, no. Servo, Jimmy Rogers was more like this.
I think it was higher. I think it was like...
This? Yo-don't lady, yo-don't lady, yo-don't lady.
What are you doing? Stop it this instant.
Can't you see you're killing observer?
Devils, devils.
What, what? It's just a little yodeling.
Yeah, like Jimmy Rogers.
What, you guys never heard of music?
That's not music, that's vomitus.
We have a rich tradition of old ballads spanning the century.
Yeah, I bet you do.
I'd like to hear what kind of Schoenberg, Milton, Babbitt crap you can groan at.
Well, I'm glad you asked.
Here's a little number we wrote during the brain wars of Columba.
We discern it goes a little something, just like this.
There was a time so bright and gay
It seems like only yesterday
When I held your brain in my arms
Your adrenaline was like wine
Sweet perfume was your end of pride
When I held your brain in my arms
But now your brain is gone and it's left an empty hole
I gaze into your sockets, but you're just a hollow skull
I used to love Allah, your medulla oblongata
And your basal ganglia
I remember we would stroll
Along your fissure of Rolando
When I held your brain in my arms
I miss how we would float down your vestibular canal
And how we would go swimming in your ponds
The music you would play on your locust corolles
Still tickles my neurons
Now I'm sorry that I dropped you
That I accidentally plopped you
When I held your brain in my arms
It caused a contusion
During suddenly Susan
When I held your brain in my arms
[Music]
Well, that was lovely.
Eh, not bad.
Yeah, well, you know, we got some good songs too, like Cherry Pie and Silver Thunderbird.
Yeah, oh, and what's that one Asia song?
[Music]
No, no, no, it hurts.
We'll be right back.
[Music]
Tell you about the house.
Bob, come here.
Are we growing hats?
There's something there.
What's that?
Are you sure you don't need the scuba gear to look at it?
Tell Miss October I love her.
Bob Guccione will show up for the funeral.
Donations in lieu of flowers should be sent to Bodacious Tata's monthly.
Same kind of burns, that's all Victor's on.
You don't think he was drowned?
No, no, he was already dead when he was thrown into the water.
Thrown? You don't think it was some kind of wild animal?
Whatever killed Angelo had the cunning to try to conceal its victim.
How's Victor?
He's all right. He wants to talk to you.
We'll be right there.
It's Angelo.
You shouldn't have done that.
Good idea.
He says he knows what killed him.
Or Angelo's gonna hit that big quarter booth in the sky.
Just a typical morning for Tom Waits.
Anyway, after I succeeded in bringing through that cat, I knew I was on the right track.
It was just a matter of pushing the apparatus to its limits.
Cat? You call that horrible thing a cat?
Well, it's cat-ish.
I thought that I'd contacted savages and that cat was something their witch doctors had made.
Nobody made it that way. It was born that way. It's a mutation, a freak.
Caused by excess radiation in the atmosphere.
You're dropping to be 20.
That explains that woman.
Dressed like Pagliacci.
Nice.
If she came from the same place that that cat did, it's a wonder you could still recognize her as a woman.
Give me 50 burpees.
The cat's body is still extremely radioactive. You're lucky your burns weren't even more serious.
Don't worry about me.
It's that creature, that woman I'm worried about.
Can I watch Nickelodeon?
I'll be alright in a little while and we can go after her.
No, you won't. Dr. Blair is sending over a nurse and you're gonna stay in bed and do just what she says.
I wish she were here already. It'll be dark soon.
We've got to do something about that creature.
He's right, Professor. We've got to stop her from getting off this island before she goes and kills somebody else.
Now slump some more, let your arms just hang down there and don't move.
Florence Nightstalker.
What'd they drop her off in Nicaragua?
She gets to tend to the victims of the Crimean War.
Never get off the gosh darn boat. Absolutely golly darn right.
RuPaul.
Comprehensive healthcare on the bayou. Comprehensive healthcare on the bayou.
Louise Fletcher is Clara Barton as Florence Nightingale in The Piano II, Southern Comfort.
And she didn't take the paved path because...
Prelude to the afternoon of the nurse.
Stashu Perretna.
Which means eggnog. Give me your eggnog.
Stashu Perretna Blanca. I'm just a bird in the sky.
What do you want? You're speaking English.
Double dur-hay.
Of course I'm speaking English. What did you expect?
But the letters on the key were in Greek.
Key? What key?
Who are you? What do you want?
Who's your main provider?
No, wait. You must help me.
I lost my retainer.
No. Stay away from me.
What do you mean?
Your face. No. Stay away from me.
Real sensitive nurse. Stay away. You're unattractive.
Angela would have loved this part.
It's a creature with 5,000 yards rushing.
Just need to make a copy of your insurance card. I'll be right back.
We have a hard target search on a licensed practical nurse.
The sick and frail nurse of the herd.
Do you have an appointment? We're running an hour behind.
I hope the creature has really cold hands when she kills them.
She's really tucking into that nurse out there.
That sounded like a woman screaming.
Yes. You got a gun in the house?
Only my 20-gauge shotgun I use for ducks.
Let's take it with us just in case.
All right. Better put on our anti-radiation suits.
Because we have those now. Apparently.
I think she was delicious.
Forced facials.
Just relax. Just let the tension go.
You're a dead nurse with no cares.
Okay. Now this product has a defoliant.
I really love it.
I see. She's Martin Landau.
Clint Howard mask.
Dick Smith from the year 5000.
Sinus pain can feel like a sparkle up your nose.
Can I borrow your face? Thanks.
Okay. Now you won't feel a thing, but you'll notice you're missing your face.
These symptoms should go away.
She made a creepy crawler.
Just wear my radiation sundress.
Okay. Here's your radiation rubbers.
I'm Tara from the year 5000 called in sick.
I'm Tara from the year 4543.
Stashu.
Stashu. Corretta. I mean, you called for a nurse?
It's just a makeup line. Not where my face ends.
Hi.
You were expecting me?
Of course. Come in. You must be the nurse.
No. I'm Fred Dreyer. Yes, I'm the nurse, you dope!
You'll be happy to know your patient is much better.
We were expecting you earlier.
Yes, but it's all right. You came just in time.
Now I won't be so frightened when you have to leave.
The nurse is coming from inside the house.
We're making gravy in our pants.
You don't blame me for what I did?
Bed-wetting isn't your fault.
Of course not. How could you ignore another human being's cry for help?
Well, gee, Wally, do all humans cry out for help?
Fine.
You're a very remarkable woman. Very unusual.
Perhaps more unusual than you realize.
I have L.A. nails.
Your hands.
I thought you were Dale.
You went there like the woman's last night.
I had to gather you, Dimble.
Don't be afraid. Look at me.
This is making me clammy-er.
Am I so terrifying?
I have to ask my mom. Mom!
The face last night, it was...
Does this?
Does this bug you?
Money makes the veil go round.
It was...
If you will listen, I shall explain.
I got a booger on my finger and I can't get it off.
Bob Mackie's Ku Klux Klan.
Be very quiet. We're hunting isotopes.
Due to the ever-increasing amount of radioactivity in the atmosphere,
by the year 5000, every fifth child born was a mutant.
Are your nails dry yet?
Unable to cure these freaks,
our rulers put them in special isolated colonies.
Called day cares.
It was one of these colonies that your apparatus probed.
And one of those poor unfortunates whose image you saw last night.
But you...
What can I, as a simple weenie, do about it?
How did you get here?
I was selected to come and lead you into our world of the future.
You must come with me.
We need you.
You have to help us move our couch.
Why?
Only with new blood.
With undamaged preatomic genes.
Can we hope to break the terrible hereditary chain
of more and more mutants born into each generation.
Hi, we found a dead faceless nurse out in the woods.
Know anything about it?
Hey, you, don't splay, pal.
Everything all right?
We're getting along splendidly.
He wants me.
Why don't you try and get some sleep?
'Cause it's noon.
Very well.
First I think I'll get you some fresh water.
And pour it over your slutty face.
Mm-hmm.
Harlan. Jezebel.
Home wrecker. Man stealer.
Skag. Thick ankle, slight mustache.
Oh, I'm sorry, how clumsy.
No!
What does that mean? I don't know.
Claire will cut.
What? What?
I just got the picture.
What?
I must have been dreaming.
Victor, are you all right?
I'm hypnotizing you, you dope!
Oh, I puked in my lap again.
Oh!
Be a lady. Keep your legs together.
I think I'd better stay with him for a while.
No!
All right, girl, fine!
It is better that he sleep.
Please leave us now.
Wow, nurses ruled back then.
They would periodically declare martial law.
Yeah.
Well, I want to go home now.
I'm tired and I have enough candy, I think.
Breaker one-nine, this is the moist boy calling all truckers.
It's a blonde Maryland quail.
Honey, is this too much for the PTA meeting?
What do you think, the head, the sandal toe or the pump?
It protects me from the radioactivity.
You must put on something to do the same.
I got a lead-lined bar jacket in here somewhere.
So, you like the year 5000 and lots of cool bars and stuff?
Anyway, I'm going to dump the ice princess.
I mean, we've never had a single satisfying sexual encounter that I would...
What are you doing?
I'm in the future. I must go.
I'm broasting for comfort.
Yeah, we really didn't need the rubber underwear, did we?
You don't know what you're saying. You're ill. You should be in bed.
No, I must go.
Leave him alone.
You're fired.
Another egg. I knew there was more.
Healthcare worker without a face.
What could have happened?
Who do you suppose she is? There's no...
Pencils, cheese, batteries, what?
She must be the nurse.
The nurse that Dr. Blair was sending over.
But the nurse came to the house.
We'd better get back there.
Let's walk incredibly slowly back to the house.
Victor, listen to me. She's hypnotized you. You don't know what you're doing.
You don't understand, Claire. I've got to go. They need help.
Oh, Victor, you're all confused.
It's you who are confused.
No, I call it's you.
It really records how the women of the 20th century stood idly by
while the atmosphere was contaminated...
Message coming in.
...and the children of the future doomed.
She's right, Claire.
If she's so right, why did she have to hypnotize you?
I warn you, don't force me to kill again.
Again?
You. You're that thing that killed Angelo.
I did not wish to. He surprised me.
He would have spoiled my mission.
The cunning Angelo.
Did you? Now what do you think of your angel of mercy?
Actually, let's get this straight.
A vicious woman comes in the year 5000 and slaps people?
Yeah, it's the plot so far.
Can I have my faith back?
Attracted member of British royalty.
Can this marriage be saved?
Now this is terror. Do I lie, huh?
Do I lie, huh, people?
Why is it screening terror?
Finally, a radioactive duck to shoot at.
Soooowy, big, big, big, big.
Sooowy.
No, don't do that.
Yes, a tiny sliver of payback from this movie.
Yes, thank you.
I'm going to reset the VCR.
Are you sure he's dead?
Dead.
Both dead.
The VCR experience a major loss today.
Electrocuted.
It was pure moisture, the perfect conduit.
It just bought a short circuit at the Chamber's voltage.
She said every fifth child was being born that way.
Well, that explains Adam Sammler and Jim Carrey.
Is that what the future holds? More like her?
She shouldn't have played hockey.
We've got to reach them, Professor.
See to it they get the necessary hereditary genes they need.
Do you suppose we could repair the machine, perfect it?
So that a man could travel through and return?
I won't have a boyfriend!
Others like her will come. There may be millions of them.
Boy!
We've got to do something clear after all we are human beings.
You're right, Buzz.
So you do it.
But there's another way.
Ham?
The future is what we make it.
Wait a minute, I'm full of crap.
Whether there will be creatures like her.
I like milk!
Especially you, Bob.
All of us.
On mankind.
On what we do.
Remember, moisturize and use a sunscreen!
And don't bob for french fries.
Marry only UL approved attractive people!
Good night!
Jeez, what's the big deal, Mike?
It's nothing. I just want to know how many times you took Ginger out.
Well, I didn't exactly take her out, if you know what I mean, my friend.
You didn't exactly take her out, you mean you.
I'm a Dutch treat, my friend.
So you fancy yourself as something of a ladies man, then?
Oh, I think the ladies themselves fancy me as something of a ladies man, my friend.
So what if I set you up on a blind date with a real hot tomato?
Well, I think I could handle it, my friend, my friend.
Alrighty, then you think you could be ready in...
Ready, willing and able, Mike.
Just dial her up here and...
Wow, he's going to bring you honey from across time!
Maybe Theo Patcher or Mary Todd Lincoln!
Or all of the gold diggers of 1933, maybe!
Bring 'em all on, my friend!
And we're all set!
Whoa! Get away from me! Get away from me!
Oh, Mike, that is rich! I guess I needed a little lesson.
Oh, that's great.
So, where to, sweetie?
Perkins it is, then! Bread, bowl, salads for two!
Alright, have fun! And hey, don't let her rip your face off!
I won't! Mike, the peepers won't!
Ah, that was a good one.
Please, we are not peepers, we're observers.
There is a victor!
Excellent! Give her the sword!
Now, you must vanquish your opponent.
Vanquish, shway?
You have earned his death.
Well, I'd really just rather have an all-sport.
By our law that you terminate the hairy one. Use the sword!
Well, okay.
No. I won't.
It is required by your laws, not ours.
We are human.
We may not have evolved to your level of intelligence yet.
And yes, we often stumble in our quest to do right.
But at least we strive for compassion.
For kindness.
And yes, for love.
There, I've said it and I wouldn't take it back.
Being human isn't about killing in cold blood those who are helpless.
Though I have in fact done that, I probably shouldn't have.
Being human is about watching the sun rise and set.
About the quality of mercy and yes, again, about love.
Being human isn't about eating lots of pills and carrying your brain around in a salad bowl.
Being human is about the feeling one gets when you see what you do.
You forgot I'm not human!
Oh, that tears it, Megillah. You are so dead, I can't believe it!
It may be time to end this, Observers.
Shall I schedule the dissections?
Excellent idea, Observers.
Thank you, Observer. And you too, Observer.
Tune in next week.
Observe your local listings.
I'll skewer you, you big sticky cheater!
(Music)
Produced in association with the Sci-Fi channel.